If this is your first Nanodegree program, you start here.
如果这是你的第一个 Nanodegren 计划 你就从这里开始
If you've taken a Nanodegree program with us before,
如果你以前和我们一起做 Nanogren 计划
you already know a little bit of what to expect.
你已经知道了点什么
Udacity is always improving our learning experience for students.
Udacity 总是提高我们对学生的学习体验
So you can watch this to see what has changed or you can skip ahead.
因此 您可以观看此内容以查看已更改的内容或您可以向前跳过的内容
You can also download the transcript of this video in the resources tab.
您还可以在 " 资源 " 选项卡中下载此视频的抄本
Let's get started. We truly believe that
我们开始吧 我们真的相信
you couldn't have chosen a better place to learn.
你无法选择一个更好的地方去学习
A lot of people have worked tirelessly to create
很多人孜孜不倦地创作
the course material and platform features,
课程材料和平台特点
as we all want you to get the most of your learning journey.
因为我们都希望你能得到最重要的学习旅程
Our pledge is to provide you with resources and
我们的承诺是向您提供资源和
services that will further enable you to succeed in your Nanodegree program.
将使您能够在 Nanodegren 计划中获得成功
As you go through the lessons,
当你吸取教训时
you may find some to be difficult and may feel discouraged.
你可能会觉得有些困难 可能会觉得灰心丧气
If this happens, we encourage you to take advantage of
如果发生这种情况 我们鼓励您利用
your community channels and mentor services to help clarify the concepts,
您的社区渠道和导师服务 以帮助阐明概念
or just to share your doubts.
或者只是分享你的疑惑
Our mentors are there to help you.
我们的导师是来帮你的
You will get advice and guidance to ensure
您将获得建议和指导以确保
that you are on track to complete the projects.
您正在跟踪完成这些项目
We want you to succeed and graduate with the Udacity Nanodegree certificate.
我们希望您能够获得成功 并获得 " udacity 纳米级证书 "
We value the trust you have put in us by making this investment in your future career.
我们珍视你对我们的信任 在你的未来事业中做出这一投资
We take it very seriously and we're here to help
我们非常重视这一问题
you achieve whatever you came here to accomplish.
你就能达到你来到这里的目的